questions = {
    "Q01": {
        "Question": "The common element which describe the web page, is ?",
        "Answer1": "heading",
        "Answer2": "paragraph",
        "Answer3": "list",
        "Answer4": "All of these",
        "Solution": "All of these"
    },
    "Q02": {
        "Question": "HTML stands for?",
        "Answer1": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        "Answer2": "High Text Markup Language",
        "Answer3": "Hyper Tabular Markup Language",
        "Answer4": "None of these",
        "Solution": "Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    "Q03": {
        "Question": "which of the following tag is used to mark a begining of paragraph ?",
        "Answer1": "<TD>",
        "Answer2": "<br>",
        "Answer3": "<P>",
        "Answer4": "<TR>",
        "Solution": "<P>"
    },
    "Q04": {
        "Question": "From which tag descriptive list starts ?",
        "Answer1": "<LL>",
        "Answer2": "<DD>",
        "Answer3": "<DL>",
        "Answer4": "<DS>",
        "Solution": "<DL>"
    },
    "Q05": {
        "Question": "Correct HTML tag for the largest heading ?",
        "Answer1": "<head>",
        "Answer2": "<h6>",
        "Answer3": "<heading>",
        "Answer4": "<h1>",
        "Solution": "<h1>"
    },
    "Q06": {
        "Question": "The attribute of <form> tag ?",
        "Answer1": "Method",
        "Answer2": "Action",
        "Answer3": "Both method and action",
        "Answer4": "None of these",
        "Solution": "Both method and action"
    },
    "Q07": {
        "Question": "Markup tags tell the web browser ?",
        "Answer1": "How to organise the page",
        "Answer2": "How to display the page",
        "Answer3": "How to display message box on page",
        "Answer4": "None of these",
        "Solution": "How to display the page"
    },
    "Q08": {
        "Question": "www is based on which model ?",
        "Answer1": "Local-server",
        "Answer2": "Client-server",
        "Answer3": "3-tier",
        "Answer4": "None of these",
        "Solution": "Client-server"
    },
    "Q09": {
        "Question": "What are Empty elements and is it valid ?",
        "Answer1": "No, there is no such terms as Empty Element",
        "Answer2": "Empty elements are element with no data",
        "Answer3": "No, it is not valid to use Empty Element",
        "Answer4": "None of these",
        "Solution": "Empty elements are element with no data"
    },
    "Q10": {
        "Question": "Which of the following attributes of text box control allow to limit the maximum character ?",
        "Answer1": "size",
        "Answer2": "len",
        "Answer3": "maxlength",
        "Answer4": "all of these",
        "Solution": "maxlength"
    },
    "Q11": {
        "Question": "Web pages starts with which ofthe following tag ?",
        "Answer1": "<Body>",
        "Answer2": "<Title>",
        "Answer3": "<HTML>",
        "Answer4": "<Form>",
        "Solution": "<HTML>"
    },
    "Q12": {
        "Question": "HTML is a subset of",
        "Answer1": "SGMT",
        "Answer2": "SGML",
        "Answer3": "SGMD",
        "Answer4": "None of these",
        "Solution": "SGML"
    },
    "Q13": {
        "Question": "Which of the following is a container ?",
        "Answer1": "<SELECT>",
        "Answer2": "<Value>",
        "Answer3": "<INPUT>",
        "Answer4": "<BODY>",
        "Solution": "<SELECT>"
    },
    "Q14": {
        "Question": "The attribute, which define the relationship between current document and HREF'ed URL is ?",
        "Answer1": "REL",
        "Answer2": "URL",
        "Answer3": "REV",
        "Answer4": "all of these",
        "Solution": "REL"
    },
    "Q15": {
        "Question": "<DT> tag is designed to fit a single line of our web page but <DD> tag will accept a",
        "Answer1": "line of text",
        "Answer2": "full paragraph",
        "Answer3": "word",
        "Answer4": "request",
        "Solution": "full paragraph"
    }
}